https://ballyhoocreations.com/privacy-policy/

About Ballyhoo
FAQ (Frequently Asked Questions)
About Ballyhoo
FAQ (Frequently Asked Questions)
Who we are
Ballyhoo Creations is run by sole proprieter Luci Ayyat in Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, USA.
Our website address is: http://ballyhoocreations.com.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
Image uploads are not currently enabled for this website.  For future use, if you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
All information entered into a contact for or email newsletter signup is maintained by Ballyhoo Creations.  No contact information is shared or sold outside of this business.  We use security software on this WordPress installation website to protect user data.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Google analytics is active on this site.  It may use tracking cookies to track your web behaviour on this site and other places on the internet.
Who we share your data with
Nobody.  Your information is either kept by Ballyhoo Creations, or passed to a 3rd party by your request such as when you pay with your choice of payment gateway – Ballyhoo Creations does not recieve or store your credit card or payment information.  That is all handled by the 3rd party payment processor such as Amazon Pay, Square Pay or Paypal.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
How we protect your data
This site is protected by Securi Security Software for wordpress to prevent hackers and malicious attacks.  No payment information is used or stored by us, we only record your order history for digital files so you may come back and download at any time.  Comments, contact forms or newsletter signups are protected behind a firewall and strong password protection.
Latest Videos
Investigate
Search
Navigate
Menu
Home
Shop
Account details
FAQ (Frequently Asked Questions)
All images and text on this site are Copyright Ballyhoo Creations 2020
Ballyhoo Creations website is powered by Wordpress, WooCommerce and Elementor Pro.
Join the Crew for Free Projects
Thanks for the message.
I'll reply as soon as possible.
